walkinfreshers.net 2017-11-20

# Privacy Policy of walkinfreshers.net - Walkin Freshers

Privacy Policy of walkinfreshers.net

The privacy of our visitors is of main importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.walkinfreshers.net and how it is used. The privacy policy document here we afford for intimating you about how we work on our job portal. This portal reflects the information collected from various websites. So, when one who is applying for a job or about to attend any walkin, based on the information provided in our portal is requested to verify the same from various other sites or from the official website. We don’t assure that the data provided here is completely correct. One can use the information at their own risk. We are not responsible for any consequences that occur on applying for any job or walkins data that we provided in our portal.

walkinfreshers.net is website created as a resource to help people know about latest recruitment, exams and results, answer key, admit cad etc. The site primarily focused on Walkins for freshers, walkins Drive, Off-campus Drive, Government jobs, Bank Jobs, Civil Engineering Jobs, jobs for freshers, and more. It intends to be a great platform for job seekers without getting involved in legal suits. So, here is the disclaimer policy for www.walkinfreshers.net, almost care is generally taken while we are publishing the information in our portal. Our source of collecting information is completely from other websites. There might be some mistakes in our portal which are made unknowingly because the effort is made completely by humans.

Click any link at your own risk in our portal. We are not responsible for any loss you get on doing so. We don’t have control on the portal as these are maintained by third party people. The Job seekers are advised to be careful and check the information from other websites and make conform regarding any particular advertisement.

Privacy Policy:

If you require any more information from www.walkinfreshers.net or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at support@walkinfreshers.net, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by www.walkinfreshers.net and how it is used.

Logos that we use in our jobs portal are completely collected from other websites and sometimes from the official website. We provide it for more interactive to the topic that we are providing in our portal. There is no other intention in providing the logos. Owners of the logo, please write to us if you feel that we are violating the copy write of our logo. We assure you that the logo will be removed in short span of time.

Log Files:

Like many other Web sites, walkinfreshers.net makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol -IP addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider I S P, date & time stamp, referring/ exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.  
Google as a third party vendor uses cookies to serve ads on www.walkinfreshers.net

Google use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to walkinfreshers.net and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.  
Google Adsense These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on walkinfreshers.net send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see. walkinfreshers.net has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

Google Channel Partner :

Getting the more ad units from the Google certified channel partner, ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on the walkinfreshers.net

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. walkinfreshers.net privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.
